

#### → DETAILS →

3 Street La Goulette Borj El Baccouche Ariana, Tunis, 2080,

Tunisia

+21629300943

imene.jalel@gmail.com

DATE OF BIRTH

31/08/1994

NATIONALITY

Tunisian

DRIVING LICENSE

car driving licence (category B)

LINKS .

LinkedIn

Imene Jalel

LANGUAGES

Arabic

French (DELF B2 PRO:92.5/100)

English (Toeic: 900/990)

SKILLS •

Lean Manufacturing

Project management

CMMS module in SAGE EM

Manufacturing module in SAGE EM

Inventory management module in SAGE EM

Logistics Management (Warehouse Management, Demand Planning, Materials Planning)

C#

L4G

SolidWorks: Level A Certificate

## IMENE JALEL

# Industrial and Logistics Systems Engineer

#### PROFILE

Industrial and Logistic Systems Engineer with 1-year experience as a technical-functional consultant ERP SAGE EM and 8 months as an intern in multiple multinational industries (automotive, aircraft and food industries).

I have a true passion for manufacturing systems optimization and supply chain management.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Technical-functional consultant SAGE EM at Discovery Informatique, Tunis August 2018 — Present

Managing projects from customer needs definition to developing creative and specific solutions.

#### INTERNSHIPS

#### Final project internship at Zodiac Aerospace, Tunis

February 2018 — July 2019

Optimization of the internal logistic flows from the reception of the raw material to the production system.

#### ENGINEERING INTERNSHIP at Valeo, Tunis

June 2018 — July 2018

Muda Hunting and implementation of the 5S workplace organization method.

## ENGINEERING INTERNSHIP at SOTUCHOC, Tunis

June 2017 — July 2017

Mapping SOTUCHOC's Supply Chain (VSM)

### EDUCATION

Engineering degree in Industrial and Logistics Systems Engineering, National Engineering School of Carthage, Tunis

September 2019 — July 2018

Engineering Preparatory Classes Mathematics-Physics, Preparatory Institute for Engineering Studies of Tunis (IPEIT), Tunis

September 2019 — June 2015

## **EXTRA- CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

#### General Secretary at Hayyou'Raqs Association, Tunis

January 2018 — December 2019

The Association's goal is to support and promote the Art of Choreography.

#### Web redactor at AS DU WEB, Teleworking

September 2019 — February 2018 Writing web content for several French sites

#### Classical dance teacher for beginners, Tunis

July 2014 — August 2016